upvery.com 2009-12-25

# Privacy Policy For Submitting Your Press Release News To Upvery.com

### UpVery Privacy Policy

Your privacy on the internet is very important to UpVery and we take your privacy seriously. We are committed to providing the best and safest online experience, thus please read the following to learn more about it.

**General Information**  
In order for you to register as a user on UpVery.com and to access certain materials or pages, (i.e. signup, tell a friend, and the like), we collect the following types of user information, including, but not limited to, your name, phone number and email address. We gather the information in order to contact you to provide you with further information about our company and services. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs. Under no circumstances do we divulge or sell any information about an individual user to a third party.

**Usage Tracking**  
We implement a user tracking feature, however we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. This is done regardless of whether the visitor has registered on the Site or is visiting the Site anonymously. This includes pages on our Site that you visited. We do break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, refering page, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string. The purpose of this is to analyze our users’ actions, improve your online experience, as well as help us go on building a better service for you.

**Use of Cookies.**  
We may place a "cookie", the small text file transferred by a Web Site to a computer that is browsing the Web Site. The cookie itself does not contain personal information, though it can be stored on your computer, which automatically identifies you to the Site. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. In addition, you can delete any cookies that have already been placed on your computer.

**Security**  
UpVery takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. For any additional information about the security measures we use on UpVery.com, please contact us with your questions or concerns.

**Email privacy policy**  
We'll never share or sell your email address to a third party. The only usage could be sending the free email updates you prefer, including, but not limited to, newsletters, special coverage and UpVery news etc. You can unsubscribe for any or all email lists that you previously chose to receive. But, please make sure that your account will be simultaneously removed, when you choose to unsubscribe.

**Hyperlinks policy**  
UpVery.com may contain hyperlinks to other sites. This privacy policy applies only to this Site and not to any other sites, including sites accessed by hyperlink from this Site. UpVery has no responsibility, liability for, or control over those other web sites or Internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, nor has it any control over the privacy policies of any of these sites. In order to assist in protecting the confidentiality of your personal information, UpVery applies security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. However, in light of the nature of Internet technologies, security and privacy risks cannot be eliminated and, therefore, UpVery cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy.

**Users’ Consent**  
By accessing UpVery.com, you are signifying, expressing and providing your consent to the information collection, information usage and other procedures described in the privacy policy above. If you decide to update our privacy policy, we will renew this page so that you could aware of the information we gather, use and disclose under some certain circumstances. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
